(Amy:)I mean, seriously, you have got
to let me scan your brain
(Amy:)when you're being dishonest
so I can see what lights up.
(Penny:)That's super helpful, Amy.
(Penny:)Thanks a lot.
I can't wait to do that.
(Amy:)I can see a clump of bitch cells
lightin' up from here.
(Howard:)Give me a second
to call my cousin.
(Sheldon:)I don't see how a tax lawyer
from Fort Lauderdale
(Sheldon:)could be helpful regarding
intellectual property.
(Howard:)First of all,
he's in Boca Raton,
(Howard:)which is better
than Fort Lauderdale.
(Howard:)But more importantly,
he lasted two days on Jeopardy,
(Howard:)so he's clearly a smart guy.
(Howard's cousin(on skype):)Hello.
(Howard:)Hey, Marty.
Thanks for talking to us.
(Marty:)Hey, no problem.
(Marty:)Thanks for going to outer space
so no matter what I do
(Marty:)my mom will be
disappointed in me.
(Howard:)Well, I married a little
Catholic girl, so we're even.
(Howard:)Anyway,
this is Leonard and Sheldon.
(Howard:)The three of us came up
with the guidance system.
- Hi. - Hello.
And this is my friend, Raj.
(Raj:)Oh, I'm not on the patent.
I'm just here